Deepthi Damodaran

Thrissur, Kerala deepthidamodarancu8et_g4z@indeedemail.com +917510656065

I am Deepthi Damodaran , i have strong interest in law and justice . I have participated in 3 virtual moot court and 4 offline moot court competitions ,showcasing legal research and advocacy skills . In addition i have gained valuable experience through internships at police station and various courts . I have experience as a campus ambassador at International Model United Nations . I have completed certificate courses on introduction to Advocacy from UNICEF and introductory course on climate right litigation from inforMEA.

Outside the legal field i have participated in various management events .Their diverse range of experiences has equipped with a wide range of skills . I have completed certificate course on effective leadership and successful mindset from HP LIFE .

In addition to these i have much interest in litigation and lawyering . Outside the legal realm i am an accomplished guitarist and worked as a guitar tutor helping others learn and develop their own musical abilities.

Personal Details

Date of Birth: 2000-07-07 Eligible to work in: India

Highest Career Level: 1-2 years experience

Industry: Legal

Work Experience

Campus Ambassador

International Model United Nations - Kerala October 2023 to December 2023

Legal and research Intern

Giri Iyer Associates - Kerala March 2021 to May 2021

Education

Bachelor of Business Administration and Bachelor of Legislative Law in Corporate and business law in Business Administration

University of Calicut - Calicut, Kerala June 2019 to June 2024

Certificate course in Introduction to Advocacy

UNICEF - India

Certificate in Introductory course on climate rights litigation

InforMEA - India

Certificate course in Leadership and successful mindset

HP LIFE - India

Skills / IT Skills

- Leadership
- Litigation
- Legal research
- Communication skills

Online Profile

http://linkedin.com/in/deepthi-damodaran-296b69221

Awards / Achievements

Moot court competition best memorial

Moot court competition runner up team